Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series X: Alexander for President 1996
  - Sub-series A: Press and Publications
    - Candidate Questionnaire – United We Stand – New Hampshire, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 38)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Southern States Police Benevolent Association, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 39)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Defense News, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 40)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – California Voter Guide – circa, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 41)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – East Cobber, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 42)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Burlington Free Press, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 43)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Organization for a New Equality, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 44)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Business and Industry Association of New Hampshire, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 45)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Icon, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 46)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Energy America Education Fund, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 47)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Quad-City Times, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 48)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Christian Action Network, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 49)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – New York Times, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 50)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Americans for Tax Reform, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 51)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Inc. Magazine, 1995 December (Box 405, Folder 52)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Jackson Sun – circa, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 53)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – United Council, 1996 January (Box 405, Folder 54)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Delphi Internet, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 55)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – National Minority Politics, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 56)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – The News-Herald – circa, 1995 (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Associated Press, 1996 February (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – United States Student Association, 1995 (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Electionline, 1996 (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Miami Herald, 1996 (Box 406, Folder 5)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Omaha World-Herald, 1996 January (Box 406, Folder 6)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Kyodo News Service, 1995 (Box 406, Folder 7)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Institute for Justice, 1995 (Box 406, Folder 8)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – National Association for Students for Higher Education, 1996 (Box 406, Folder 9)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – Institute for U.S. Cuba Relations, 1996 (Box 406, Folder 10)
    - Candidate Questionnaire – List of Answered Questionnaires, undated (Box 406, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 406, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1994-1995 January (Box 406, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1995 January (Box 406, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1995 February (Box 406, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1995 February-March (Box 406, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1995 March-May (Box 406, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1994-1998 (Box 406, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Catalog/Inventory of Articles, 1990-1992 (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Alexander Clippings, 1990 December 17 – 1991 March 20 (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 407, Folder 3)
    - Clippings from Republican Network Material, 1992-1994 (1 of 5) (Box 407, Folder 4)
    - Clippings from Republican Network Material, 1992-1994 (2 of 5) (Box 407, Folder 5)
    - Clippings from Republican Network Material, 1992-1994 (3 of 5) (Box 407, Folder 6)
    - Clippings from Republican Network Material, 1992-1994 (4 of 5) (Box 407, Folder 7)
    - Clippings from Republican Network Material, 1992-1994 (5 of 5) (Box 407, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 January-December (1 of 2) (Box 407, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 January-December (2 of 2) (Box 407, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 (1 of 4) (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 (2 of 4) (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 (3 of 4) (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 (4 of 4) (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 October – 1995 February (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1996 (Box 408, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 March 4 (Box 408, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 March 5-8 (Box 408, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 409, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Important Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 409, Folder 2)
    - Meet the Press with Alexander and Leon Panetta Transcript, 1994 October (Box 409, Folder 3)
    - Lexis Nexus Articles, 1995 (Box 409, Folder 4)
    - Freedom Forum Media Studies Center News, 1995 (Box 409, Folder 5)
    - State of the States Article, 1995 September (Box 409, Folder 6)
    - “Where They Stand, 1996 GOP Presidential Hopefuls and their Records on the Issues” - 1995 (Box 409, Folder 7)
  - Sub-series B: Correspondence
    - Correspondence
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 410, Folder 1)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1995 (1 of 4) (Box 410, Folder 2)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1995 (2 of 4) (Box 410, Folder 3)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1995 (3 of 4) (Box 410, Folder 4)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1995 (4 of 4) (Box 410, Folder 5)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 410, Folder 6)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 410, Folder 7)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 (1 of 3) (Box 410, Folder 8)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 (2 of 3) (Box 410, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 (3 of 3) (Box 411, Folder 1)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 January-March (1 of 5) (Box 411, Folder 2)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 January-March (2 of 5) (Box 411, Folder 3)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 January-March (3 of 5) (Box 411, Folder 4)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 January-March (4 of 5) (Box 411, Folder 5)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 January-March (5 of 5) (Box 411, Folder 6)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (1 of 19) (Box 411, Folder 7)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (2 of 19) (Box 411, Folder 8)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (3 of 19) (Box 411, Folder 9)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (4 of 19) (Box 411, Folder 10)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (5 of 19) (Box 411, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (6 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 1)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (7 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 2)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (8 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 3)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (9 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 4)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (10 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 5)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (11 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 6)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (12 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 7)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (13 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 8)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (14 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 9)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (15 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 10)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (16 of 19) (Box 412, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (17 of 19) (Box 413, Folder 1)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (18 of 19) (Box 413, Folder 2)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February (19 of 19) (Box 413, Folder 3)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February-March (1 of 8) (Box 413, Folder 4)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February-March (2 of 8) (Box 413, Folder 5)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February-March (3 of 8) (Box 413, Folder 6)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February-March (4 of 8) (Box 413, Folder 7)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February-March (5 of 8) (Box 413, Folder 8)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February-March (6 of 8) (Box 413, Folder 9)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February-March (7 of 8) (Box 413, Folder 10)
      - Constituent Correspondence, 1996 February-March (8 of 8) (Box 413, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence
      - Doug Bailey, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 1)
      - Baker, Donelson, Bearman, and Caldwell Law Firm, 1995 February 21 (Box 414, Folder 2)
      - Gary Baker, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 3)
      - Tom Beasley, 1995 January 23 (Box 414, Folder 4)
      - Mitch Daniels, 1995 February 6 (Box 414, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 6)
  - Sub-series C: State Files
    - Includes lists, contributors, funds, etc.
    - State Files
      - Alabama, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 415, Folder 1)
      - Alabama, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 415, Folder 2)
      - Alaska, 1995-1996 (Box 415, Folder 3)
      - Arizona, 1995-1996 (Box 415, Folder 4)
      - Arkansas, 1995-1996 (Box 416, Folder 1)
      - California, 1995-1996 (1 of 3) (Box 416, Folder 2)
      - California, 1995-1996 (2 of 3) (Box 416, Folder 3)
      - California, 1995-1996 (3 of 3) (Box 416, Folder 4)
      - Colorado, 1995-1996 (Box 416, Folder 5)
      - Connecticut, 1995-1996 (Box 416, Folder 6)
      - Delaware, 1995-1996 (Box 416, Folder 7)
      - District of Columbia, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 416, Folder 8)
      - District of Columbia, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 417, Folder 1)
      - Florida, 1995-1996 (1 of 3) (Box 417, Folder 2)
      - Florida, 1995-1996 (2 of 3) (Box 417, Folder 3)
      - Florida, 1995-1996 (3 of 3) (Box 417, Folder 4)
      - Georgia, 1995-1996 (1 of 3) (Box 417, Folder 5)
      - Georgia, 1995-1996 (2 of 3) (Box 417, Folder 6)
      - Georgia, 1995-1996 (3 of 3) (Box 417, Folder 7)
      - Hawaii, 1995-1996 (Box 418, Folder 1)
      - Idaho, 1995-1996 (Box 418, Folder 2)
      - Illinois, 1995-1996 (1 of 3) (Box 418, Folder 3)
      - Illinois, 1995-1996 (2 of 3) (Box 418, Folder 4)
      - Illinois, 1995-1996 (3 of 3) (Box 418, Folder 5)
      - Indiana, 1995-1996 (Box 418, Folder 6)
      - Iowa, 1995-1996 (Box 418, Folder 7)
      - Kansas, 1995-1996 (Box 418, Folder 8)
      - Kentucky, 1995-1996 (Box 418, Folder 9)
      - Louisiana, 1995-1996 (Box 418, Folder 10)
      - Maine, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 419, Folder 1)
      - Maine, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 419, Folder 2)
      - Maryland, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 419, Folder 3)
      - Maryland, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 419, Folder 4)
      - Massachusetts, 1995-1996 (Box 419, Folder 5)
      - Michigan, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 419, Folder 6)
      - Michigan, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 419, Folder 7)
      - Minnesota, 1995-1996 (Box 420, Folder 1)
      - Mississippi, 1995-1996 (Box 420, Folder 2)
      - Missouri, 1995-1996 (Box 420, Folder 3)
      - Montana, 1995-1996 (Box 420, Folder 4)
      - Nebraska, 1995-1996 (Box 420, Folder 5)
      - Nevada, 1995-1996 (Box 420, Folder 6)
      - New Hampshire, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 420, Folder 7)
      - New Hampshire, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 420, Folder 8)
      - New Jersey, 1995-1996 (Box 420, Folder 9)
      - New Mexico, 1995-1996 (Box 420, Folder 10)
      - New York, 1995-1996 (1 of 3) (Box 421, Folder 1)
      - New York, 1995-1996 (2 of 3) (Box 421, Folder 2)
      - New York, 1995-1996 (3 of 3) (Box 421, Folder 3)
      - North Carolina, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 421, Folder 4)
      - North Carolina, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 421, Folder 5)
      - North Dakota, 1995-1996 (Box 421, Folder 6)
      - Ohio, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 421, Folder 7)
      - Ohio, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 421, Folder 8)
      - Oklahoma, 1995-1996 (Box 422, Folder 1)
      - Oregon, 1995-1996 (Box 422, Folder 2)
      - Pennsylvania, 1995-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 422, Folder 3)
      - Pennsylvania, 1995-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 422, Folder 4)
      - Rhode Island, 1995-1996 (Box 422, Folder 5)
      - South Carolina, 1995-1996 (Box 422, Folder 6)
      - South Dakota, 1995-1996 (Box 422, Folder 7)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (1 of 9) (Box 422, Folder 8)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (2 of 9) (Box 422, Folder 9)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (3 of 9) (Box 423, Folder 1)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (4 of 9) (Box 423, Folder 2)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (5 of 9) (Box 423, Folder 3)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (6 of 9) (Box 423, Folder 4)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (7 of 9) (Box 423, Folder 5)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (8 of 9) (Box 423, Folder 6)
      - Tennessee, 1995-1996 (9 of 9) (Box 424, Folder 1)
      - Texas, 1995-1996 (1 of 3) (Box 424, Folder 2)
      - Texas, 1995-1996 (2 of 3) (Box 424, Folder 3)
      - Texas, 1995-1996 (3 of 3) (Box 424, Folder 4)
      - Utah, 1995-1996 (Box 424, Folder 5)
      - Vermont, 1995-1996 (Box 424, Folder 6)
      - Virginia, 1995-1996 (1 of 3) (Box 425, Folder 1)
      - Virginia, 1995-1996 (2 of 3) (Box 425, Folder 2)
      - Virginia, 1995-1996 (3 of 3) (Box 425, Folder 3)
      - Washington, 1995-1996 (Box 425, Folder 4)
      - West Virginia, 1995-1996 (Box 425, Folder 5)
      - Wisconsin, 1995-1996 (Box 425, Folder 6)
      - Wyoming, 1995-1996 (Box 425, Folder 7)
      - Foreign Countries, 1995-1996 (Box 425, Folder 8)
      - U.S. Territories, 1995-1996 (Box 425, Folder 9)
      - Mixed State Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 425, Folder 10)
      - No Addresses, 1995-1996 (Box 425, Folder 11)
  - Sub-series D: Speech Materials
    - Pre-Campaign – William Penn College Commencement, 1993 May 9 (Box 426, Folder 1)
    - Pre-Campaign – Young Republican Speech, 1993 June (Box 426, Folder 2)
    - Pre-Campaign – Address at the President’s Dinner Honoring Ronald Reagan, 1993 July 21 (Box 426, Folder 3)
    - Pre-Campaign – National Association of Life Underwriters, 1993 September 21 (Box 426, Folder 4)
    - Pre-Campaign – National Federation of Republican Women Annual Convention, 1993 September 24 (Box 426, Folder 5)
    - Pre-Campaign – Young President’s Organization, 1993 October 8 (Box 426, Folder 6)
    - Pre-Campaign – Prayer Breakfast in Manchester, New Hampshire, 1994 March 20 (Box 426, Folder 7)
    - Pre-Campaign – New Castle County Chamber of Commerce Annual Dinner, 1994 March (Box 426, Folder 8)
    - Pre-Campaign – Lincoln Day Dinner, 1994 April 16 (Box 426, Folder 9)
    - Pre-Campaign – Untitled Speech, 1994 April 21 (Box 426, Folder 10)
    - Pre-Campaign – Southern Republican Leadership Conference, 1994 April-May (Box 426, Folder 11)
    - Pre-Campaign – Miscellaneous (1 of 4) (Box 426, Folder 12)
    - Pre-Campaign – Miscellaneous (2 of 4) (Box 426, Folder 13)
    - Pre-Campaign – Miscellaneous (3 of 4) (Box 426, Folder 14)
    - Pre-Campaign – Miscellaneous (4 of 4) (Box 426, Folder 15)
    - Pre-Campaign – “What We Need to Do” Speech Drafts, 1994 January (Box 426, Folder 16)
    - Cut Their Pay, 1993-1995 (Box 426, Folder 17)
    - Sam Houston Statue Event, 1994 (Box 426, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (1 of 2) (Box 426, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (2 of 2) (Box 426, Folder 20)
    - Best Speech Notes – circa, 1994 (Box 426, Folder 21)
    - “Yesterday’s Values… Tomorrow’s Jobs”, 1986 April 8 (Box 427, Folder 1)
    - “What’s a University President Supposed to Do?”, 1990 April 20 (Box 427, Folder 2)
    - “My Minute”, 1993 (Box 427, Folder 3)
    - “Renewing the Promise of American Life”, 1993-1994 (Box 427, Folder 4)
    - Manchester Prayer Breakfast, 1994 March 20 (Box 427, Folder 5)
    - Transcript of Remarks at Southern Republican Leadership Conference, 1994 April 30 (Box 427, Folder 6)
    - Eagleburger Speech, 1995 January (Box 427, Folder 7)
    - Belmont University’s Jack C. Massey Graduate School of Business Address, 1997 (Box 427, Folder 8)
    - Education and Homeschooling, 1993-1996 (Box 427, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, 1995 January-August (Box 427, Folder 10)
    - 50th D-Day Anniversary Speech and Travel, 1994 (1 of 2) (Box 427, Folder 11)
    - 50th D-Day Anniversary Speech and Travel, 1994 (2 of 2) (Box 427, Folder 12)
    - Pre-Campaign – “The Arrogant Empire” Speech, 1994 October 28 (Box 428, Folder 1)
    - Pre-Campaign – RNC Reception, 1995 January (Box 428, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, 1993-1998 (Box 428, Folder 3)
    - CSIS – Foreign Policy, 1995 January 26 (Box 428, Folder 4)
    - “Abolishing the Department of Education in Order to Liberate Parents and Schools”, 1995 January 26 (Box 428, Folder 5)
    - Congressional Pensions, 1995 February 1 (Box 428, Folder 6)
    - Maryville Address, 1995 February 28 (Box 428, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Message, 1995 February-June (Box 428, Folder 8)
    - “Growth, Freedom, and Personal Responsibility: The Next President and the Next Century”, 1995 April 18 (Box 428, Folder 9)
    - New York University Convocation, 1995 May 15 (Box 428, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Notes, 1995 May 15 (Box 428, Folder 11)
    - “From the Road” Excerpts, 1995 May 16 (Box 428, Folder 12)
    - Miami Conference of Mayors, 1995 June 19 (Box 428, Folder 13)
    - Welfare Speech, 1995 July (Box 428, Folder 14)
    - OnlineHost Forum Question and Answer Session, 1995 (Box 428, Folder 15)
    - Alexander on the Issues – circa, 1995 (Box 428, Folder 16)
    - Statement for the National Federation of Republican Women – circa, 1995 (Box 428, Folder 17)
    - Australia Speech, 1996 June (Box 428, Folder 18)
    - Spending per Pupil and National Test Results, 1996-1997 (Box 428, Folder 19)
    - State of the State Address by Gov. Mike Huckabee, 1997 January 14 (Box 428, Folder 20)
    - National Education Report Card, 1997 February (Box 428, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Speech, 1997 March 11 (Box 428, Folder 22)
    - “Making America One Country” Draft, 1997 June (Box 428, Folder 23)
    - “Making America One Country” Speech, 1997 June 25 (Box 428, Folder 24)
    - “The New Affluent Society” Speech by Christopher DeMuth, 1997 July 15 (Box 429, Folder 1)
    - National Governor’s Association 1997 Annual Meeting Draft, 1997 July (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - National Governor’s Association 1997 Annual Meeting, 1997 July 30 (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - “Cut Their Pay and Send Them Home” Photocopy, 1997 July 30 (Box 429, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Appearances, and Possible Subjects for the Rest of 1997, 1997 August 1 (Box 429, Folder 5)
    - “Cutting Congress Down to Size: How a Part-time Congress Would Work” Photocopy, 1997 August 1 (Box 429, Folder 6)
    - Lobster Bake at Rye, New Hampshire, 1997 August 7 (Box 429, Folder 7)
    - Notes from George W. Bush, 1997 August 21 (Box 429, Folder 8)
    - Speech Concerning Reagan, 1997 August 22 (Box 429, Folder 9)
    - Midwest Republican Leadership Conference, 1997 August 23 (Box 429, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Notes, 1997 September 8 (Box 429, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Notes, 1997 September 9 (Box 429, Folder 12)
    - Speech to the Christian Coalition, 1997 September 13 (Box 429, Folder 13)
    - National Federation of Republican Women, 1997 September 28 (Box 429, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Memos, 1997 September (Box 429, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Opening Notes, 1997 September-October (Box 429, Folder 16)
    - Western States Leadership Conference, 1997 October 4 (Box 429, Folder 17)
    - “Ronald Reagan’s Crystal Ball”, 1997 October 20 (Box 429, Folder 18)
    - Sending the Right Message on Drugs, 1997 October (Box 429, Folder 19)
    - Nashua GOP Speech, 1997 November 3 (Box 429, Folder 20)
    - “The Common Sense of a Country” Draft, 1997 November 11 (Box 429, Folder 21)
    - Presbyterian Church Material, 1996-1997 (Box 429, Folder 22)
    - First Presbyterian Church Stewardship Luncheon, 1997 November 16 (Box 429, Folder 23)
    - Short Takes on Military Training, 1997 December (Box 429, Folder 24)
    - Speech on Prosperity, 1997 December – 1998 January (Box 429, Folder 25)
    - A Reawakening to Common Sense – circa, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 1)
    - Stump Speech Draft – circa, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Speech on a New Conservative Agenda – circa, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 3)
    - Chapter from Reagan’s Speaking My Mind – circa, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 4)
    - Chapter from Martin Anderson’s Revolution – circa, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 5)
    - Stories from Campmon – circa, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Note Cards – circa, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 7)
    - Mission Statement – Campaign for a New American Century, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 8)
    - An Institution at Risk – An External Communications Review of the National Education Association, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 9)
    - Localized Opening Remarks, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 10)
    - Opening with Jokes, 1997 (1 of 2) (Box 430, Folder 11)
    - Opening with Jokes, 1997 (2 of 2) (Box 430, Folder 12)
    - Senate Testimony on Creating the Best Schools in the World for D.C.’s Children, 1997 April 17 (Box 430, Folder 13)
    - Material on Charter Schools, 1997 (1 of 2) (Box 430, Folder 14)
    - Material on Charter Schools, 1997 (2 of 2) (Box 430, Folder 15)
    - Material on Education Reform, 1997 (1 of 4) (Box 430, Folder 16)
    - Material on Education Reform, 1997 (2 of 4) (Box 430, Folder 17)
    - Material on Education Reform, 1997 (3 of 4) (Box 430, Folder 18)
    - Material on Education Reform, 1997 (4 of 4) (Box 430, Folder 19)
    - Material on Health Reform, 1997-1999 (Box 430, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (1 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (2 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (3 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (4 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (5 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (6 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (7 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (8 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (9 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (10 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (11 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (12 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (13 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1997 (14 of 14) (Box 431, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 431, Folder 15)
    - Post-Campaign – Conservative Political Action Conference, 1998 January (Box 431, Folder 16)
    - Post-Campaign – Lincoln Day Dinner Speech, 1998 February 13 (Box 431, Folder 17)
    - Post-Campaign – Southern GOP Leadership Conference Remarks, 1998 February (Box 431, Folder 18)
    - Post-Campaign – Miscellaneous Speech Materials, 1998 February (Box 431, Folder 19)
    - Post-Campaign – Miscellaneous Speech Materials, 1998 March (Box 431, Folder 20)
    - Post-Campaign – New Misery Index, 1998 April (Box 431, Folder 21)
    - Post-Campaign – Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1998 (1 of 2) (Box 431, Folder 22)
    - Post-Campaign – Miscellaneous Speech Materials, circa 1998 (2 of 2) (Box 431, Folder 23)
    - Belknap County Lincoln Day Speech, 1996 February (Box 431, Folder 24)
    - Orange County GOP Speech, 1994 August 2 (Box 431, Folder 25)
    - Stand Up!, 1997 March 9 (Box 431, Folder 26)
    - Nashua GOP, 1997 (Box 431, Folder 27)
  - Sub-series E: Legal & Finance
    - April 15 Quarterly FEC Report, 1995 April (Box 432, Folder 1)
    - PIII Postcard, 1995 September 5 (Box 432, Folder 2)
    - T.Y. Shapiro for Chairing a Fundraiser, 1995 September (Box 432, Folder 3)